All right so we're making steady progress.
حسنًا، لقد أحرزنا تقدمًا ثابتًا.
So we've modified the list item layout to include an image view, and
لقد عدلنا مخطط عنصر القائمة ليتضمن صورة واجهة
we have all the correct images in the app now.
ويوجد لدينا جميع الصور الصحيحة في التطبيق الآن.
However, our list view and adapter don't know about these images just yet.
ومع ذلك، فإن واجهة القائمة والموائم لا يعرفات أي معلومات عن هذه الصور حتى الآن.
Now eventually we want to load the correct images dynamically
وفي نهاية المطاف الآن نرغب في تحميل الصور الصحيحة بشكل متميز
into each list item.
في كل عنصر قائمة.
So as the user scrolls up and
عندما يقوم المستخدم بالتمرير لأعلى
down the list of words, the correct image is displayed next to the words.
ولأسفل داخل قائمة الكلمات، يتم عرض الصورة الصحيحة بجانب الكلمات.
So let's move to step three, and modify the word class so
دعنا ننتقل إلى الخطوة الثالثة، ونعدّل فئة الكلمات
that each word is associated with an image that we just added.
بحيث ترتبط كل كلمة بإحدى الصور التي تمت إضافتها للتو.
Let's revisit our word class in the word.java file.
دعنا نذهب مرة أخرى إلى فئة الكلمات الخاصة بنا في ملف word.java.
Remember that this class represents a single vocabulary word
تذكّر أن هذه الفئة تمثل مفردات لغوية فردية
that we want the user to learn, and so
نرغب في أن يتعلمها المستخدم
far it contains an English and Miwok translation for the same word.
وحتى الآن، تحتوي على ترجمة بلغة الميوك واللغة الإنجليزية للكلمة نفسها.
So how would you go about modifying the word class to support these images?
كيف يمكنك البدء في تعديل فئة الكلمات لدعم هذه الصور؟
To help you out, I like you to answer these questions.
لمساعدتك، أريدك ان تجيب عن هذه الأسئلة.
So the first one is, what additional state would a word object contain?
السؤال الأول هو، ما الحالة الإضافية التي يتضمنها كائن الكلمات؟
Specify the data type and whether it should be public or private.
حدد نوع البيانات وما إذا كانت يجب أن تكون عامة أو خاصة.
And secondly, consider what additional methods we should have.
ثانيًا، فكّر في الوظائف الإضافية التي يجب اتباعها.
Should they be public, or private, and go ahead and
هل يجب أن تكون عامة أم خاصة وتابع ذلك
answer your questions in the boxes below.
وأجب عن الأسئلة في الخانات أدناه.
And as a hint,
وكتلميح،
check out the article provided about accessing resources in Android.
تحقق من المقال المقدم حول الوصول إلى الموارد في الآندرويد.